Thank you. My mirror-neuron subsystem suggests that this is going to replace phones in not too long. Ray, how's it going? Ray: Great. We're live today. (Applause) MG: Ray, give the crowd a gift of the holographic brain we saw from the video earlier. Guys, this is not only going to change phones, it's also going to change the way we collaborate. Thank you so much. Thanks, Ray. Ray: You're welcome. (Applause) MG: So folks, this is the message that I discovered in that bar in 2011: The future of computers is not locked inside one of these screens. It's right here, inside of us. (Applause) So if there's one idea that I could leave you with here today, it's that the natural machine is not some figment of the future, it's right here in 2016. Which is why all hundred of us at Meta, including the administrative staff, the executives, the designers, the engineers -- before TED2017, we're all going to be throwing away our external monitors and replacing them with a truly and profoundly more natural machine. Thank you very much. (Applause) Thank you, appreciate it. Thanks, guys. Chris Anderson: So help me out on one thing, because there've been a few augmented reality demos shown over the last year or so out there. And there's sometimes a debate among technologists about, are we really seeing the real thing on-screen? There's this issue of field of view, that somehow the technology is showing a broader view than you would actually see wearing the glasses. Were we seeing the real deal there? MG: Absolutely the real deal. Not only that, we took extra measures to shoot it with a GoPro through the actual lens in the various videos that you've seen here. We want to try to simulate the experience for the world that we're actually seeing through the glasses, and not cut any corners. CA: Thank you so much for showing us that. MG: Thanks so much, I appreciate that.
Merci. Mon système de neurones miroirs suggère que cela va remplacer les téléphones dans peu de temps. Ray, comment ça va ? Ray : Très bien. Nous sommes en direct aujourd'hui. (Applaudissements) MG: Ray, donne au public un cadeau du cerveau holographique que nous avons vu plus tôt. Ceci va non seulement remplacer les téléphones, mais cela va changer également notre manière de collaborer. Merci beaucoup. Merci, Ray. Ray : De rien. (Applaudissements) MG: Bon, voici le message que j'ai découvert dans un bar en 2011 : le futur des ordinateurs n'est pas bloqué à l'intérieur de l'un de ces écrans. Il est juste là, en nous. (Applaudissements) S'il n'y a qu'une seule idée que je peux donner aujourd'hui, c'est que la machine naturelle n'est pas le fruit du futur, elle est juste ici en 2016. C'est pourquoi nous tous à Meta, incluant le personnel administratif, les cadres, les designers, les ingénieurs -- avant TED2017, nous allons tous mettre à la poubelle nos moniteurs externes et les remplacer par des machines vraiment et profondément plus naturelles. Merci beaucoup. (Applaudissements) Merci, c'est très gentil. Merci à tous. Chris Anderson : Bon, expliquez-moi une chose, parce qu'il y a eu peu de démonstrations sur la réalité augmentée l'année dernière ou précédemment ici-même. Et il y a parfois un débat parmi les technologistes pour savoir si nous voyons vraiment l'objet réel à l'écran. C'est un problème de champ de vision. D'une certaine manière, la technologie montre une vue plus large que celle que vous devriez voir en portant les lunettes. Avons-nous vu la vraie vie ? MG : Absolument la vraie vie. Et pas seulement cela, nous avons pris d'autres mesures pour filmer avec une GoPro avec les vraies lentilles, les différentes vidéos diffusées. Nous voulons essayer de simuler l'expérience du monde que nous voyons à travers les lunettes, et ne couper aucun passage. CA : Merci beaucoup pour cette présentation. MG : Merci beaucoup, c'était un plaisir.